https://www.renin.com/terms-conditions/

Skip to content
FREE Shipping on ALL Orders!
Close main menu
Terms & ConditionsHome Terms & Conditions TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE
PLEASE READ THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE.
These Terms and Conditions of Use (the “Terms of Use”) govern your use of the www.renin.com website (the “Website”) owned and controlled by Renin Corp. (“Renin”). If you do not accept the Terms of Use, do not use the Website. By using the Website you are indicating your acceptance to be bound by the terms of these Terms of Use and the terms of the Privacy Policy available here. Renin may revise and update these Terms of Use from time to time and at any time, without notice, and in its sole discretion. If Renin decides to change these Terms of Use, Renin will post a new version on the Website and update the date set forth above. Any changes or modifications to these Terms of Use will be effective upon posting of the revisions. Your continued use of the Websites following posting of any changes or modifications constitutes your acceptance of such changes or modifications and if you do not agree with these changes or modifications, you must immediately cease using the Website. For this reason, you should frequently review these Terms of Use to understand the terms and conditions that apply to your use of the Website.
The term “you” as used herein refer to all individuals and/or entities accessing this Website for any reason.
Intellectual Property Rights in the Content
Renin either owns, or has permission to use, all content on this Website (including the underlying HTML, text and images) (the “Content”) and all intellectual property rights in that Content. All rights reserved by Renin and its licensors.
Limited License
Renin grants to you a limited license for your personal, non-commercial or educational purposes only, to display the Content on your computer, print, download and use the Content, provided that: (a) you do not modify any such Content; and (b) you include with and display on each copy of such Content the associated copyright notice. No other use is permitted. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, you may not: (a) make any commercial use of the Content or any portion thereof; (b) include any portion of the Content in or with any product that you create or distribute; or (c) copy any portion of the Content onto any other website. Nothing in these Terms of Use shall be construed as assigning or transferring any right in the Content.
Trademarks
The trademarks and trade names appearing on this website are owned by Renin or its licensors. The display of trademarks or trade names on this Website does not convey or create any license or other rights in these marks or names. Any unauthorized use of these marks or names is strictly prohibited.
No Warranties
THE INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE IS PROVIDED “AS IS” AND WITHOUT ANY WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, EITHER EXPRESS, LEGAL OR IMPLIED. RENIN SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY AND ALL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, ALL IMPLIED OR LEGAL WARRANTIES AND CONDITIONS OF QUALITY, MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE AND NON-INFRINGEMENT.
RENIN DOES NOT WARRANT THAT THE CONTENT OF THE WEBSITE (INCLUDING ANY INFORMATION, IMAGES, PHOTOS, VIDEO, MATERIAL OR DOWNLOADABLE CONTENT ACCESSED FROM OR THROUGH THE WEBSITE) WILL BE ACCURATE, UNINTERRUPTED, OR FREE FROM DEFECTS, VIRUSES OR OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS, THAT VIRUSES OR ERRORS WILL BE CORRECTED, OR THAT THE WEBSITE OR SERVER UPON WHICH IT RESIDES ARE FREE FROM VIRUSES OR ANY OTHER HARMFUL COMPONENTS. YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE IS COMPLETELY AT YOUR OWN RISK. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL RENIN, ITS AFFILIATED COMPANIES, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED TO THE USE OF THE WEBSITE, THE MATERIALS OR CONTENT ON THE WEBSITE, A DELAY OR INABILITY TO USE THE WEB SITE OR OTHERWISE ARISING IN CONNECTION WITH THE SITE, WHETHER BASED IN CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY OR OTHERWISE, EVEN IF RENIN HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH DAMAGES.
Exclusive Jurisdiction
Renin is headquartered in Brampton, Ontario, Canada. These Terms of Use, and any matter applicable to your direct or indirect use of this Website, shall be governed by the laws of the Province of Ontario and the Federal laws applicable in the Province of Ontario. Any dispute shall be settled in the Courts located in the Province of Ontario, though the foregoing shall not limit the ability of Renin from seeking injunctions and remedies in other jurisdictions which are required to stop continuing breaches of these Terms of Use by you.
Unsolicited Ideas
Renin does not accept or consider unsolicited ideas, including for the development, manufacture or marketing of products, technologies or services. Please do not submit any unsolicited ideas. If you send us your ideas despite of our request, then you agree (irrespective of what your submission states) that your submissions and their contents will automatically become the property of Renin, without any compensation to you, that Renin may use the submission and its content for any purpose and in any way, and that there is no obligation for Renin to keep the submission confidential or to make use of it.
Linking to 3rd Party Sites
Renin does not make, and expressly disclaims, any warranty or condition, express, legal or implied, statutory or otherwise, as to third party sites you link to through the Website, including but not limited to, any warranties or conditions of quality, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title or non-infringement. Further, Renin does not provide any representation or warranty with respect to the purposes for which your personal information may be used if made available, or is otherwise accessible, by virtue of you accessing such sites. We do not control the use that may be made by others of the information that you provide when you are accessing such third party websites. Renin’s Privacy Policy does not apply to third party websites including those which may be embedded into our Website. In no event shall Renin be liable for damages arising out of, or in connection with, your linking to these third party sites.
Personal Information
Personal information provided by users of the Website is subject to the terms of the Privacy Policy of Renin available here.
Contact Us
If you have any questions concerning these Terms of Use, please contact info@renin.com.
Close pop-up window
Get 10% OFF Your First Purchase!
Subscribe to our newsletter to receive product updates, exclusive deals, AND 10% OFF your first order!
Email *
Required
Consent *
Required By clicking Submit, I agree to receive marketing emails from Renin. *
RequiredCAPTCHA
Submit
This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
When you sign up, you agree to receive marketing emails from Renin. You can unsubscribe at any time.
